Guide to The Alfred C. Berol Collection of Lewis Carroll 1845 - 1993 MSS 057
© 2012 Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series 1: Correspondence
  - Subseries 1A: Correspondence from Charles L. Dodgson
    - Dodgson, Charles To Terry, Marion Als, 4pp Christ, Church, Oxford, November 14, 1882 With envelope. 5.25 x 6.75 (Cohen pg. #: 470)., 1476 (Box 4, Folder 375)
    - Dodgson, Charles to Terry, Marion "Lewis Carroll"s Letters to Marion Terry, 1869-1897" Red Leather Album with 10 letters.. (Box 4, Folder 376)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Terry, Marion Als, 3pp The Chestnuts, Guildford, August 2, 1869 (V 84) With envelope. Pasted in red leather album of letters. 6 x 8 (Cohen pg. #: 133)., 1481 (Box 4, Folder 376)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Terry, Marion Als, 3pp Christ, Church, Oxford, December 24, 1878 (V 85) Pasted in red leather album of letters. 6.25 x 7.75 (Cohen pg. #: 322)., 1485 (Box 4, Folder 376)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Terry, Marion Als, 1p [n.p.] January 17, 1879 (V 86)Originally Enclosed with Lanrick game pasted on next page of album. Pasted in red leather album of letters. 6.25 x 7.75., 1490 (Box 4, Folder 376)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Terry, Marion Als, 4pp 7 Lushington Road, Eastbourne, August 2, 1878 (V 87) Pasted in red leather album of letters. 7 x 9 (Cohen pg. #: 312)., 1493 (Box 4, Folder 376)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Terry, Marion Als, 2pp Christ, Church, Oxford, February 8, 1881 (V 88) Pasted in red leather album of letters. 6 x 8 (Cohen pg. #: 407)., 1499 (Box 4, Folder 376)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Terry, Marion AD, illus [n.p., n.d.] (V 89) With envelope. Pasted in red leather album of letters. 5 x 8., undated; 1502 (Box 4, Folder 376)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Terry, Marion Als, 3pp Christ, Church, Oxford, February 14, 1887 (V 90) Pasted in red leather album of letters. 7 x 9 (Cohen pg. #: 663)., 1503 (Box 4, Folder 376)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Terry, Marion ALs, 4pp Christ, Church, Oxford, April 3, 1892 (V 91) Pasted in red leather album of letters. 7 x 9 (Cohen pg. #: 897)., 1507 (Box 4, Folder 376)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Terry, Marion ALs, 2pp Christ, Church, Oxford, November 18, 1895 (V 92) Pasted in red leather album of letters. 3.5 x 5.25 (Cohen pg. #: 1077)., 1512 (Box 4, Folder 376)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Terry, Marion ALs, 1p Christ, Church, Oxford, October 26, 1897 (V 93) With envelope. Pasted in red leather album of letters. 3.5 x 5.25., 1515 (Box 4, Folder 376)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Tidy, Kathleen ALs, 4pp Christ, Church, Oxford, March 30, 1861 (XIX 450) 7 x 9 (Cohen pg. #: 49)., 1518 (Box 4, Folder 377)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Todd, W.E. ACs, 2pp Christ, Church, Oxford, February 9, 1882 (XIX 476) 3 x 4.75., 1523 (Box 4, Folder 378)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Todd, Mrs. W.E. ALs, 1p Christ, Church, Oxford, April 4, 1876 (XIX 477) With envelope.. 5.25 x 6.75., 1526 (Box 4, Folder 379)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Todd, Mrs. W.E. ALs, 2pp Christ, Church, Oxford, March 18, 1880 (XIX 478) With envelope.. 6 x 8 (Cohen pg. #: 379)., 1527 (Box 4, Folder 380)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Todd, Mrs. W.E. ALs, 4pp The Chestnuts, Guildford, Jan 5, 1884 (XIX 479) 5.25 x 6.75 (Cohen pg. #: 523)., 1530 (Box 4, Folder 381)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Vibert, Janet ALs, 3pp Christ, Church, Oxford, May 28, 1896 (329) 5.25 x 7 (Cohen pg. #: 1091)., 1535 (Box 4, Folder 382)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Walters, H.L.M. ALs, 2pp The Chestnuts, Guildford, January 5, 1898 (XIX 564) 7 x 9 (Cohen pg. #: 1154)., 1539 (Box 4, Folder 383)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Ward, Mrs. E.M. ALs, 2pp Christ, Church, Oxford, January 23, 1888 (XIX 511) 5.25 x 6.75 (Cohen pg. #: 692)., 1542 (Box 4, Folder 384)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Ward, Mrs. E.M. ALs, 2pp 7 Lushington Road, Eastbourne, August 26, 1888 (XIX 512) 7 x 9 (Cohen pg. #: 716)., 1545 (Box 4, Folder 385)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Ward, Mrs. E.M. ALs, 3pp Christ, Church, Oxford, January 10, 1892 (XIX 541) 5.25 x 6.75 (Cohen pg. #: 884)., 1548 (Box 4, Folder 386)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Ward, Mrs. E.M. ALs, 1p Christ, Church, Oxford, January 15, 1892 (XIX 516) With envelope. Envelope is incorrectly numbered XIX 511. 5.5 x 7., 1552 (Box 4, Folder 387)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Ward, Mrs. E.M. ALs, 2pp 7 Lushington Road, Eastbourne, October 3, 1895 (XIX 513) With envelope. 4.5 x 7 (Cohen pg. #: 1074)., 1553 (Box 4, Folder 388)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Ward, Mrs. E.M. ALs, 2pp 7 Lushington Road, Eastbourne, October 6, 1895 (XIX 514) With envelope. 4.25 x 7 (Cohen pg. #: 1074)., 1556 (Box 4, Folder 389)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Ward, Mrs. E.M. ALs, 2pp 7 Lushington Road, Eastbourne, October 8, 1895 (XIX 515) 4.25 x 7 (Cohen pg. #: 1075)., 1559 (Box 4, Folder 390)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Ward, Mrs. E.M. ALs, 2pp Christ, Church, Oxford, January 27, 1896 (XIX 542) 4.25 x 7., 1562 (Box 4, Folder 391)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Webb, Miss ALs, 3pp Christ, Church, Oxford, Monday, 6:30, [February 20, 1888] (XIX 520) 5.25 x 6.75 (Cohen pg. #: 697)., 1565 (Box 4, Folder 392)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Webb, Miss ALs, 2pp Christ, Church, Oxford, April 26, 1888 (XIX 521) 5.5 x 7 (Cohen pg. #: 702)., 1569 (Box 4, Folder 393)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Webb, Miss ALs, 2pp Christ, Church, Oxford, April 29, 1888 (XIX 522) 5.5 x 7 (Cohen pg. #: 702)., 1572 (Box 4, Folder 394)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Whatford, Jack Henry ALs, 2pp 7 Lushington Road, Eastbourne, September 24, 1892 (XIX 548) 5.5 x 7 (Cohen pg. #: 929)., 1575 (Box 4, Folder 395)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Wilcox, Mrs. W.E., "Fanny" ALs, 3pp Christ, Church, Oxford, February 7, 1877 (XII 167) 6 x 8 (Cohen pg. #: 269)., 1579 (Box 5, Folder 396)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Wilcox, Mrs. W.E., "Fanny" ALs, 3pp Christ, Church, Oxford, March 8, 1885 (XII 168) 7 x 9 (Cohen pg. #: 563)., 1583 (Box 5, Folder 397)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Wilcox, Mrs. W.E., "Fanny" ALs, 3pp Christ, Church, Oxford, December 16, 1885 (XII 169) With envelope. 6 x 7.5 (Cohen pg. #: 612)., 1587 (Box 5, Folder 398)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Wilcox, Mrs. W.E., "Fanny" ALs, 1p Christ, Church, Oxford, January 29, 1886 (XII 170) With envelope. 5.25 x 6.5 (Cohen pg. #: 618)., 1591 (Box 5, Folder 399)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Wilcox, Mrs. W.E., "Fanny" ALs, 2pp Christ, Church, Oxford, February 5, 1886 (XII 171) 5.25 x 6.5., 1592 (Box 5, Folder 400)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Wilcox, Mrs. W.E., "Fanny" ALs, 3pp Christ, Church, Oxford, February 18, 1886 (XII 172) With envelope. 7 x 9 (Cohen pg. #: 621)., 1595 (Box 5, Folder 401)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Wilcox, Mrs. W.E., "Fanny" ALs, 1p Christ, Church, Oxford, March 29, 1886 (XII 173) 4.5 x 7 (Cohen pg. #: 629)., 1599 (Box 5, Folder 402)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Wilcox, Mrs.W.E., "Fanny" ALs, 3pp Christ, Church, Oxford, June 1, 1886 (XII 174) With envelope.. 5.25 x 6.75., 1600 (Box 5, Folder 403)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Wilcox, Mrs.W.E., "Fanny" ALs, 2pp Christ, Church, Oxford, February 21, 1887 (XII 175) With envelope. 4.5 x 7 (Cohen pg. #: 666)., 1604 (Box 5, Folder 404)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Wilcox, Mrs.W.E., "Fanny" ALs, 3pp Christ Church, Oxford, February 6, 1889 (XII 176) With envelope. 6 x 7.75 (Cohen pg. #: 728)., 1607 (Box 5, Folder 405)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Wilcox, Mrs.W.E., "Fanny" ALs, 2pp Christ Church, Oxford, February 8, 1889 (XII 177) With envelope. 7 x 9 (Cohen pg. #: 728)., 1611 (Box 5, Folder 406)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Wilcox, Mrs.W.E., "Fanny" ALs, 1p Christ Church, Oxford, May 24, 1889 (XII 178) 5.5 x 7., 1614 (Box 5, Folder 407)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Wilcox, Mrs.W.E., "Fanny" ALs, 2pp Christ Church, Oxford, May 28, 1889 (XII 179) 4.5 x 7 (Cohen pg. #: 741)., 1615 (Box 5, Folder 408)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Wilcox, Mrs.W.E., "Fanny" ALs, 4pp Christ Church, Oxford, November 30, 1889 (XII 180). 5.5 x 7 (Cohen pg. #: 765)., 1618 (Box 5, Folder 409)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Wilcox, Mrs. W.E., "Fanny" ALs, 1p Christ Church, Oxford, December 5, 1890 (XII 181) 4.5 x 7., 1623 (Box 5, Folder 410)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Wilcox, Mrs. W.E., "Fanny" ALs, 1p Christ Church, Oxford, December 6, 1890 (XII 182) Docketed on verso. 6 x 3.75., 1624 (Box 5, Folder 411)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Wilcox, Mrs. W.E., "Fanny" ALs, 3pp Christ Church, Oxford, June 15, 1891 (XII 183) With envelope. 5.5 x 7 (Cohen pg. #: 846)., 1627 (Box 5, Folder 412)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Wilcox, Mrs. W.E., "Fanny" ALs, 3pp Christ Church, Oxford, November 26, 1891 (XII 184) With envelope.. 5.5 x 7 (Cohen pg. #: 874)., 1631 (Box 5, Folder 413)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Wilcox, Mrs. W.E., "Fanny" ALs, 3pp Christ Church, Oxford, December 25, 1891 (XII 185) With envelope. 5.5 x 7 (Cohen pg. #: 877)., 1635 (Box 5, Folder 414)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Wilcox, Mrs. W.E., "Fanny" ALs, 4pp Christ Church, Oxford, February 4, 1892 (XII 186) 5.5 x 7 (Cohen pg. #: 891)., 1639 (Box 5, Folder 415)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Wilcox, Mrs. W.E., "Fanny" ALs, 1p Guildford, December 22, 1893 (XII 187) 4.5 x 7., 1644 (Box 5, Folder 416)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Wilcox, Mrs. W.E., "Fanny" ALs, 2pp Christ Church, Oxford, July 3, 1894 (XII 188) With envelope. 4.5 x 7 (Cohen pg. #: 1028)., 1645 (Box 5, Folder 417)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Wilcox, Mrs. W.E., "Fanny" ALs, 1p Christ Church, Oxford, October 22, 1895 (XII 190) 4.5 x 7., 1648 (Box 5, Folder 418)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Wilcox, Mrs. W.E., "Fanny" ALs, 2pp Christ Church, Oxford, March 6, 1897 (XII 191) 3.75 x 6., 1649 (Box 5, Folder 419)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Wilcox, Mrs. W.E., "Fanny" ALs, 1p The Chestnuts, Guildford, January 4, 1898 (XII 193) 4.5 x 7 (Cohen pg. #: 1154)., 1652 (Box 5, Folder 420)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Wilcox, Mrs. W.E., "Fanny" ALs, 1p Christ Church, Oxford, Wednesday, 10 a.m. [n.d.] (XII 192) With envelope.. 3.5 x 5.25., undated; 1578 (Box 5, Folder 421)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Wilcox, Menella ALs, 3pp Grosvenor House, 44 Grand Parade, Eastbourne, July 14, 1877 (XIX 474) Possibly refers to Poem Nella"s Song. See Manuscripts. 7 x 9 (Cohen pg. #: 279)., 0592 (Box 5, Folder 422)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Wilcox, Menella ALs, 2pp 7 Lushington Road, Eastbourne, July 20, 1886 (XIX 473) Possibly refers to Poem Nella"s Song. See Manuscripts. 6 x 4 (Cohen pg. #: 633)., 0596 (Box 5, Folder 423)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Wilcox, William E. ALs, 11pp Christ Church, Oxford, May 11, 1859 (336) 7 x 9 (Cohen pg. #: 35)., 1675 (Box 5, Folder 424)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Wilcox, William M. ALs, 3pp Christ Church, Oxford, October 30, 1876 (XIX 466) 6 x 7.75., 1653 (Box 5, Folder 425)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Wilcox, William M. ALs, 3pp Christ Church, Oxford, November 23, 1880 (XIX 467) 6 x 8 (Cohen pg. #: 393)., 1657 (Box 5, Folder 426)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Wilcox, William M. ALs, 4pp Christ Church, Oxford, November 25, 1880 (XIX 468) 6 x 8 (Cohen pg. #: 394)., 1661 (Box 5, Folder 427)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Wilcox, William M. ALs, 3pp Christ Church, Oxford, June 7, 1881 (XIX 469) 6 x 7.75 (Cohen pg. #: 431)., 1666 (Box 5, Folder 428)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Wilcox, William M. ALs, 4pp 7 Lushington Road, Eastbourne, September 10, 1885 (XIX 470) 7 x 9 (Cohen pg. #: 602)., 1670 (Box 5, Folder 429)
    - Dodgson, Charles to Wilcox, Mrs. W.E. Envelope (1) (XII 189)., undated (Box 5, Folder 430)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Yonge, Charlotte ALs, 2pp Christ Church, Oxford, December 8, 1877 (XIX 475) 6 x 7.75 (Cohen pg. #: 290)., 1687 (Box 5, Folder 431)
    - Dodgson, Charles To "Dolly" [?] PLs, 4pp Christ Church, Oxford, April 5, 1882 No number. Circular letter re: an edition of Shakespeare for girls. 7 x 9, 1690 (Box 5, Folder 432)
    - Dodgson, Charles To "The Editor of the Standard" ALs, 1p [n.p.] December 10, 1893 (I 28) 9 x 5.5, 1692 (Box 5, Folder 433)
    - Dodgson, Charles To "Professor" ALs, 2pp Christ Church, Oxford, January 30, [n.y.] (XIX 539) 5.25 x 3.5, undated; 1693 (Box 5, Folder 434)
    - Dodgson, Charles To "Sir" ALs, 4pp 7 Lushington Road, Eastbourne, September 17, 1894 Detailed discussions of math and logic. 11.75 x 8.75, 1696 (Box 5, Folder 435)
    - Dodgson, Charles ALs, 1pp To "Sir" 7 Lushington Road, Eastbourne, September 17, 1894 Detailed discussions of math and logic. 11.75 x 8.75, 1698 (Box 5, Folder 436)
  - Subseries 1B: Correspondence to Charles L. Dodgson
    - Beach, Sir Michael Hicks to Dodgson, Charles ALs, 3pp Board of Trade, Whitehall Gardens, May 28, 1892 (XV 274) Marked "78507". 7.25 x 9.5, 2073 (Box 5, Folder 437)
    - Darwin, G.H. to Dodgson, Charles ALs, 3pp Nice, January 30, 1885 (XV 250) 6.5 x 8.25, 2077 (Box 5, Folder 438)
    - du Maurier, George to Dodgson, Charles ALs, 3pp 91 Great Russell Street, December 23, [n.y.] (XV 240) 7 x 9, undated; 2081 (Box 5, Folder 439)
    - Frost, Arthur Burdett to Dodgson, Charles ALs, 4pp n.p., May 5, 1881 (XV 251) Marked "36802" 8 x 10, 2085 (Box 5, Folder 440)
    - Furniss, Harry to Dodgson, Charles ALs, 3pp 23 St. Edmund"s Terrace, Regent"s Park, March 2, 1885 (XV 275)Marked "49533". 7 x 9, 2090 (Box 5, Folder 441)
    - Furniss, Harry to Dodgson, Charles ALs, 7pp 23 St. Edmund"s Terrace, Regent"s Park, April 8, 1885 (XV 276) Marked "49958". 7 x 9, 2094 (Box 5, Folder 441)
    - Furniss, Harry to Dodgson, Charles ANs, 2pp 23 St. Edmund"s Terrace, Regent"s Park, June 13, 1885 (XV 277). 7 x 9, 2101 (Box 5, Folder 441)
    - Furniss, Harry to Dodgson, Charles ALs, illus, 4pp Kent, August 23, 1886 (XV 278) Marked "54696". 7 x 9, 2104 (Box 5, Folder 441)
    - Furniss, Harry to Dodgson, Charles ALs, illus, 8pp 23 St. Edmund"s Terrace, Regent"s Park, October 10, 1889 (XV 279) Marked "67067". 8 x 10, 2109 (Box 5, Folder 441)
    - Furniss, Harry to Dodgson, Charles ALs, 1p 23 St. Edmund"s Terrace, Regent"s Park, November 8, n.y. (XV 280)Marked "84666". 8 x 10, undated; 2118 (Box 5, Folder 441)
    - Holman-Hunt, W. to Dodgson, Charles ALs, 3pp [T]or Villa, Cam[p]den Hill, Kensington W., July 24, 186[1] (XV 234) 5.5 x 7, 2119 (Box 5, Folder 442)
    - Holman-Hunt, W. to Dodgson, Charles ALs, 3pp 3 Wilton Terrace, Campden Hill W., February 7, 1873 (XV 235) Marked "14963". 7 x 9, 2123 (Box 5, Folder 442)
    - Holman-Hunt, W. to Dodgson, Charles ALs, 3pp Draycott Lodge, Fulham, June 26, 1895 (XV 236)Marked "90389". 7 x 8.75, 2126 (Box 5, Folder 442)
    - Prince Leopold to Dodgson, Charles ALs, 4pp Claremont, Esher, December 22, 1889 (XV 252) Marked "68703". 7 x 9, 2130 (Box 5, Folder 443)
    - Prince Leopold to Dodgson, Charles ALs, 3pp [n.p.] Feb 2, 1876 (XV 253). 7 x 9, 2135 (Box 5, Folder 443)
    - Liddell, H.G. to Dodgson, Charles ALs, Christ Church, Oxford, November 6, 1890 (XV 288) Marked "72524". 5.25 x 3.25, 2139 (Box 5, Folder 444)
    - Liddell, H.G. to Dodgson, Charles ALs, 1p Christ Church, Oxford, November 7, 1890 (XV 287) Numbered "72542". 5.25 x 3.25, 2140 (Box 5, Folder 444)
    - Liddell, H.G. to Dodgson, Charles ALs, 1p Christ Church, Oxford, November 27, 1890 (XV 290)Marked "72713" 6 x 4, 2141 (Box 5, Folder 444)
    - Liddell, H.G. to Dodgson, Charles ALs, 1p Christ Church, Oxford, March 9, 1891 (XV 289) Marked "73737". 6 x 4, 2142 (Box 5, Folder 444)
    - Liddell, H.G. to Dodgson, Charles ALs, 1p Christ Church, 5 p.m. [n.d.] (XV 291) 6 x 4, undated; 2143 (Box 5, Folder 444)
    - Millais, J.E. to Dodgson, Charles ALs, 1p 7 Cromwell Place, South Kensington, September 26, 1864 (XV 241). 7 x 4.5, 2144 (Box 5, Folder 445)
    - Millais, J.E. to Dodgson, Charles ALs, 1p 7 Cromwell Place, South Kensington, December 14, [1865] (XV 242). 7 x 4.5, 2145 (Box 5, Folder 445)
    - Millais, J.E. to Dodgson, Charles ALs, 2pp [n.p.] September 2, 1886 (XV 243). 6 x 3.75, 2146 (Box 5, Folder 445)
    - Millais, J.E to Dodgson, Charles ALs, 1p 7 Cromwell Place, South Kensington, July 9, 1870 (XV 244). 5.25 x 3.5, 2149 (Box 5, Folder 445)
    - Millais, J.E. to Dodgson, Charles ALs, 2pp 7 Cromwell Place, South Kensington, [July 25, n.d.] (XV 245) 5.25 x 3.5, undated; 2150 (Box 5, Folder 445)
    - Patmore, Coventry to Dodgson, Charles ALs, 2pp Hastings, March 7, 1890 (XV 281) Marked "69490". 7 x 4.5, 2153 (Box 5, Folder 446)
    - Patmore, Coventry to Dodgson, Charles ALs, 1p Hastings, June 12, 1891 (XV 282) Marked "74597". 8 x 5, 2154 (Box 5, Folder 446)
    - Reed, B. German to Dodgson, Charles ALs, 2pp The Old Ship Hotel, Brighton, February 2, 187[3] (XV 273) Marked "14935". 7 x 4.5, 2155 (Box 5, Folder 447)
    - Reed, B. German to Dodgson, Charles ALs, 4pp [Garrick Club], June 5, 1873 (XV 272) Marked "15726". 7 x 9, 2158 (Box 5, Folder 447)
    - Rossetti, Christina to Dodgson, Charles ALs, 2pp 30 Torrington Square, London, [n.d.] (XV 232) 7 x 4.5, undated; 2163 (Box 5, Folder 448)
    - Rossetti, Dante Gabriel to Dodgson, Charles ALs, 4pp 16 Cheyne Walk, Chelsea, December 21, 1863 (XV 238) 7 x 9, 2165 (Box 5, Folder 449)
    - Ruskin, John to Dodgson, Charles ALs, 1p Corpus Christi College, Oxford [n.d.] (XV 246). 7 x 4.5, undated; 2170 (Box 5, Folder 450)
    - Ruskin, John to Dodgson, Charles ALs, 2pp November 23, [n.y.] (XV 247) Marked "21019". 7 x 9, undated; 2171 (Box 5, Folder 450)
    - Ruskin, John to Dodgson, Charles ALs, 1p Brantwood, Coniston, Lancashire, [n.d.] (XV 248) Marked "43152". 7 x 4.5, undated; 2174 (Box 5, Folder 450)
    - Ruskin, John to Dodgson, Charles ALs, 1p Brantwood, Coniston, Lancashire [n.d.] (XV 249) Marked "45395". 7 x 9, undated; 2175 (Box 5, Folder 450)
    - Salisbury, Lord George to Dodgson, Charles ALs, 3pp Hatfield, August 9, [n.y.] (XV 259) Marked "27200". 7 x 9, undated; 2176 (Box 5, Folder 451)
    - Salisbury, Lord George to Dodgson, Charles ALs, 1p Hatfield House, Hatfield, Herts., [n.d.] (XV 260) Marked "5195". 7 x 4.5, undated; 2180 (Box 5, Folder 451)
    - Salisbury, Lord George to Dodgson, Charles ALs, 1p Hatfield House, Hatfield, Herts., [n.d.] (XV 261) Marked "25936". 7 x 4.5, undated; 2181 (Box 5, Folder 451)
    - Salisbury, Lord George to Dodgson, Charles ALs, 3pp 20 Arlington Street, S.W., May 21, [1881] (XV 262)Marked "36835". 7 x 9, 2182 (Box 5, Folder 451)
    - Salisbury, Lord George to Dodgson, Charles ALs, 3pp Hatfield House, Hatfield, Herts., Jan 31, 188[3] (XV 263) Marked " 38701". 7 x 9, 2186 (Box 5, Folder 451)
    - Salisbury, Lord George to Dodgson, Charles ALs, 2pp 20 Arlington Street, S.W. 7 x 4.5, undated; 2190 (Box 5, Folder 451)
    - Salisbury, Lord George to Dodgson, Charles ALs, 20 Arlington Street, S.W., July [4], [1884] (XV 265) Marked "47465". 7 x 4.5, 2193 (Box 5, Folder 451)
    - Salisbury, Lord George to Dodgson, Charles ALs, 1p 20 Arlington Street, S.W., November 3, [1884] (XV 266) Marked "48430". 7 x 4.5, 2196 (Box 5, Folder 451)
    - Salisbury, Lord George to Dodgson, Charles ALs, 1p 20 Arlington Street, S.W., March 10, [1866] (XV 268)Marked "60899". 7 x 9, 2197 (Box 5, Folder 451)
    - Salisbury, Lord George to Dodgson, Charles ALs, 3pp Hatfield House, Hatfield, Herts., August 31, [1895] (XV 270) Marked "90859". 7 x 9, 2198 (Box 5, Folder 451)
    - Salisbury, Lord George to Dodgson, Charles ALs, 3pp Chalet Cecil, Puys pres Dieppe, September 6, 1895 (XV 271) Marked "90918". 7 x 4.5, 2202 (Box 5, Folder 451)
    - Salisbury, Lord George to Dodgson, Charles ALs, Hatfield House, Hatfield, Herts., April 20, [n.y.] (XV 267). 7 x 9, undated; 2206 (Box 5, Folder 451)
    - Salisbury, Lord George to Dodgson, Charles ALs, 1p 20 Arlington Street, S.W., [May] 11, [n.y.] (XV 269)Marked "82590" 7 x 9, undated; 2210 (Box 5, Folder 451)
    - Taylor, H. to Dodgson, Charles ALs, 2pp The Uplands, East [Sheen], September 1, 1862 (XV 237) 7 x 9, 2211 (Box 5, Folder 452)
    - Tenniel, Sir John to Dodgson, Charles ALs, 1pp Portsdown Road, April 4, [n.y.] (XV 283) 7 x 9, undated (Box 5, Folder 452.A)
    - Tenniel, Sir John to Dodgson, Charles ALs, 1pp Portsdown Road, Maida Hill W., July 22, 1890, [ (XV 284) 7 x 4.5 (Box 5, Folder 452.B)
    - Tenniel, Sir John to Dodgson, Charles ALs, 1pp Portsdown Road, Maida Hill W., July 4, 1893 (XV 285) 7 x 4.5 (Box 5, Folder 452.C)
    - Tenniel, Sir John to Dodgson, Charles ALs, 1pp Portsdown Road, Maida Hill W., September 9, 1896 (XV 286) 7 x 9 (Box 5, Folder 452)
    - Terry, Ellen to Dodgson, Charles ALs, 3pp 33 Longridge Road, South Kensington, March 15, 1883 (XV 292) Marked "42712". 6 x 8, 2215 (Box 5, Folder 453)
    - Terry, Ellen to Dodgson, Charles ALs, 4pp Tuesday [n.p., n.d.] (XV 293) Marked "42081". 7 x 9, undated; 2219 (Box 5, Folder 453)
    - Terry, Ellen to Dodgson, Charles ALs, 5pp The Crown Hotel, Seven Oaks, May 26, 1884 (XV 294)Both sheets marked "47109". 7 x 4.5, 2224 (Box 5, Folder 453)
    - Terry, Kathleen to Dodgson, Charles ALs, 2pp [n.p.] Saturday, June 8, 1868 (XV 239) 7 x 9, 2230 (Box 5, Folder 454)
    - Watts, G.F. to Dodgson, Charles ALs, 2pp Little Holland House, July 15, 1864 (XV 258) 8.25 x 5.25, 2233 (Box 5, Folder 455)
    - Yates, Edmund to Dodgson, Charles ANs, 1p 3 Abbey Road, St. John"s Wood, N.W. (XV 233) 7 x 4.5, undated; 2236 (Box 5, Folder 456)
    - Yonge, Charlotte to Dodgson, Charles ALs, 2pp Elderfield, Otterbourne, Winchester, February 23, 1878 (XV 254) Marked "26661" 7 x 9, 2237 (Box 5, Folder 457)
    - Yonge, Charlotte to Dodgson, Charles ALs, 1p Elderfield, Otterbourne, Winchester, January 15, 1880 (XV 255). 5.5 x 7.25, 2240 (Box 5, Folder 457)
    - Yonge, Charlotte to Dodgson, Charles ALs, 1p Elderfield, Otterbourne, Winchester, May [15][n.y.] (XV 256) Marked "36749". 7.25 x 4.5, undated; 2241 (Box 5, Folder 457)
    - Yonge, Charlotte to Dodgson, Charles ALs, 3pp Elderfield, Otterbourne, Winchester, December [30, n.y.]] (XV 257) "Marked 85573". 5.5 x 3.5, undated; 2242 (Box 5, Folder 457)
  - Subseries 1C: Other Contemporary Correspondence.
    - De La Mare, Walter to Shawyer, Mrs. TLs, 1p Hill House, Taplow, Buckinghamshire, September 27, 1932 (XII 218) See Manuscripts File:. (Box 5, Folder 458)
    - De La Mare, Walter to Shawyer, Mrs. TLs, 1p Hill House, Taplow, Buckinghamshire, October 27, 1932 (XII 219) See manuscript file titled Miscellaneous Memoirs of Charles Dodgson. (Box 5, Folder 458)
    - Dodgson, Menella to Stevens, Mrs. N.H. ALs, 3pp The Chestnuts, Guildford, January 17, 1898 (XIII 207) (Box 5, Folder 459)
    - Dodgson, Wilfred to Stevens, Mrs. N.H. ALs, 3pp Christ Church, Oxford, February 5, 1898 (XIII 207) With envelope. See picture file: Stevens (Box 5, Folder 460)
    - Furniss, Harry to Edward Russell ALs, illus, 1p 23 St. Edmund"s Terrace, Regent"s Park, N.W., August 5, 1885. (Box 5, Folder 461)
    - Furniss, Harry to Edward Russell ALs, illus, 1p Garrick Club, January 28, 1902. (Box 5, Folder 462)
    - Maitland, Alice to [Rees, Reverend A. Williams] ALs, 8pp 1 Chatsworth Villas, Old Bath Road, Cheltenham, February 8, 1899 (XVI 295)With envelope. See manuscript file titled Miscellaneous Memoirs of Charles Dodgson. (Box 5, Folder 463)
    - Terry, Ellen to Rix, Lottie ALs, 2pp [22 Barkston Gardens, Earls Court, S.W., December 20, 1892]. (Box 5, Folder 464)
    - Terry, Ellen to Rix, Mrs. ALs, 2pp 22 Barkston Gardens, Earls Court, S.W., January 11, 1893. (Box 5, Folder 464)
  - Subseries 1D: Calling Cards
    - Ruskin, John Calling Card Denmark Hill "John Ruskin" With penciled notes., undated (Box 5, Folder 465)
    - Ruskin, John Card "Mr Ruskin"s,/Tea and Coffee Shop/.."., undated (Box 5, Folder 466)
    - Ruskin, Mrs. Calling Card "Mrs Ruskin" Black border., undated (Box 5, Folder 467)
    - Ruskin, Mrs. Calling Card "Mrs Ruskin" Black border., undated (Box 5, Folder 468)
    - Watson, Lady Calling Card Peacehaven, Sussex "Lady Watson" With penciled note, undated (Box 5, Folder 469)
- Series 2: Manuscripts
  - Subseries 2A: Manuscripts by Charles L. Dodgson.
    - Dodgson, Charles "A 12 fold Division of Magnitudes.. " Ms, 1p [Christ Church], Oxford, Nov 11, 1886 Christ Church Common Room Weekly Bill on verso. 5.75 x 11.25, 1703 (Box 6, Folder 470)